vystarcu.org 2002-05-03

# VyStar | Privacy Notice

     | 

**_PRIVACY NOTICE_**

VyStar Credit Union and its affiliate VyStar Financial Group, LLC (herein referred to as **_we, our,_** or **_us_** ) understand and recognize the sensitivity of your personal financial information and take every effort to ensure that your private information is protected. Your privacy is a top priority. This notice describes how we protect your nonpublic personal financial information. We are required by law to give you this privacy notice to explain how we collect, use, and safeguard your personal financial information.

We are committed to providing you with competitive products and services to meet your financial needs, which necessitates that we share information about you to complete your transactions and to provide you with certain financial opportunities. In order to do so, we have entered into agreements with other companies that provide either services to us or additional financial products for you to consider. We may also share information about you with our affiliated third party financial service providers, which provide insurance, brokerage, and credit union services.

Under these arrangements, we may disclose all of the information we collect, as described below, to companies that perform marketing or other services on our behalf, or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements, or to our affiliated third party financial service providers. To protect your privacy, we only work with companies that agree to maintain strong confidentiality protections and limit the use of the information we provide. We do not permit these companies to sell to other third parties the information we provide to them.

**Information We Collect And Disclose About You**

We collect the following nonpublic personal information about you from a variety of sources and may disclose all the information we collect to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf, or to other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements, or to our affiliates, except that the only information we will disclose to our affiliates is information solely as to transactions or experiences between you and us. 

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms, such as name, address, social security number, and income. 
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others that work closely with us to provide you with financial products, as account balances, payment history, parties to transactions, and credit card usage. 
  * Information we receive from a consumer-reporting agency, such as your creditworthiness and credit history. 
  * Information obtained from verifying the information you provide on an application or other forms, such as from your current or past employers or from other institutions where you conduct financial transactions.

We may also disclose any nonpublic information about you under other circumstances as permitted or required by law, typically to process transactions on your behalf, conduct our operations, follow your instructions as you authorize, or to protect the security of our financial records.

If you decide to terminate your membership or become an inactive member, we will adhere to the privacy policies and practices described in this notice.

**How We Protect and Restrict Your Account Information**

We restrict access to your personal and account information to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information. When visiting our web site (www.vystarcu.org), you will be asked for personal information. This information will be used to serve your needs quickly and identify other products and services we may offer you in the future. For more details, please visit our web site and view our online privacy policy.

* * *

Your privacy and financial success are our concern. We are committed to protecting your privacy and will take every reasonable step to ensure your personal information is protected.

If you have any further questions regarding our privacy practices or policy, you can reach us:

Via the Internet at [www.vystarcu.org](http://www.vystarcu.org/pub/default.asp)

By Telephone for VyStar Credit Union at (904) 777-6000 or 1-800-445-6289, extension 3 and ask for an Account Representative

By Mail for VyStar Credit Union at P. O. Box 45085, Jacksonville, FL 32232-5085

By Telephone for VyStar Financial Group, LLC at (904) 908-2495 or (904) 908-2496 and ask for a Registered Financial Representative

By Mail for VyStar Financial Group, LLC at P.O. Box 45257, Jacksonville, FL 32232-5257

ACCOUNT DISCLOSURE  |  PRIVACY STATEMENT  |   [CONTACT US](mailto:info@vystarcu.org)  |   HOME

©2002 VyStar Credit Union.  
P.O. Box 45085, Jacksonville, Florida 32232-5085  
  
---|---
